My Sister in Law is a comedy film directed by Lucio Fulci.
Intransigent magistrate Viola Orlando is targeted by her rivals who set her twin sister Rosa — a high-class
prostitute and pornographic photo-novel star — up to impersonate Viola and demolish her reputation.
To complicate things even further, Viola is torn between enforcing the law or
giving up her seat on the bench to marry her childhood friend.
Judge Viola Orlando / Rosa Orlando, played by Edwige Fenech.
Raffaele Esposito, played by Raf Luca.
Count Renato Altero, played by Giancarlo Dettori.
Bortolon, played by Mario Maranzana.
The prosecutor, played by Carlo Sposito.
Zaganella, the chancellor, played by Walter Valdi.
My Sister in Law (Italian: La pretora, lit.
'The Magistrate') is an Italian commedia sexy all'italiana
directed by Lucio Fulci and starring Edwige Fenech.
The tone is lighthearted.